[Music]
you
I'm so excited I can't believe that my
sisters are coming to visit for the
whole [ __ ] weekend I haven't seen
either of them in years well I can't
believe you have a couple of sisters and
never even mention them how come we
never see them around Mindy oh you know
how it is Sonia one of my sisters has
been on the run from the police for as
long as I can remember it's really hard
for my family to get together when one
of my sisters is always behind bars ha
ha
you know Manic if Mindy's sisters are
anything like her you might be able to
convince one of them to let you [ __ ]
them in the ass or if they're all [ __ ]
you might be able to talk those [ __ ]
into sucking your big hairy balls at the
same [ __ ] time
what a little sister slike Mindy the
Jews about them are a terrible obvious
us because euros bish well for starters
my favorite sister is named Mundy she
was my best friend growing up she really
knew how to [ __ ] party one time in
kindergarten the two of us got in
trouble for having sex with every single
kid on the playground Mundy would still
have sex with the other kids even when
they would beg her to stop haha that's
so funny I almost [ __ ] my pants from
laughing but what about your other
sister didn't you say there were two of
them what is the other one like oh man
the other one's name is Flora what I
[ __ ] hate the [ __ ] Flora thinks she
is better than everyone and just because
she is waiting for sex until marriage I
just wished she would hurry up and
commit suicide awesome [ __ ] now now
Minnie calm your big juicy pits I get
that you and Manny don't agree with
Flora's lifestyle but she's still your
sister
a virgin Alok attacks is putting up that
the mostly owner of municipal fully sexy
system
[Applause]
you
[Music]
holy [ __ ] you mean to tell me that sexy
witch with the big boobs is Mindy's
sister
Mundy Nadja oh my God it's been so long
sorry I took so long getting here Mindy
I had the taxi driver pull over behind
KFC so I could sell his penis ha ha
you're crazy Mandy you haven't changed
one bit rum since we were kids hey isn't
this green man your boyfriend you told
me all about he sexier [ __ ]
do you think I could sell his balls
right [ __ ] now damn bro you sure know
how to pick em you absolute madman
ha ha there will be plenty of time just
up his balls over the weekend Mandy
right now we still need to wait for our
other sister Flora to arrive what did
you just say Mindy are you [ __ ] you
[ __ ] [ __ ]
why would you invite her here we hate
her remember did you forget about that
time three years ago where she called
the police on me for losing in her
biscuits and gravy now Mandy I'm going
to tell you the same thing I just told
your sister Flora is family and family
shouldn't fight your aunt Flora have
your differences but I'm sure Flora
loves you too more than anybody else in
this world
besides we all know for it was in the
right for calling the police on you that
day it's nice to meet you Mandy my name
is Sonia Mindy is my best friend in the
whole wide world and my name is Sonic
Sonic the Hedgehog this is my bro Manic
but you already know that don't you [ __ ]
and this man right here is well he's my
boyfriend
Bart Levy Montclair of Dresden he is the
richest and most sexiest man in the
entire world I love him with all of my
pathetic little heart he completes me
look Mandy there's a taxi driving up
from down the street I bet that's Laura
you
Mindi my dear sister I feel like it's
been forever since I've seen you how are
you doing shut the [ __ ] up you damn
[ __ ] you're not even our biological
sister you freak
you know we hate you so just get lost
you were adopted
you know you're not a real part of this
family so why do you act like it
[ __ ] make like a bakery truck and move
your buns back home and thus far away
from us that's possible before I rip
your head off Maundy calm down that's
enough no what I say will never be
enough it's because of this [ __ ] that
are not committed suicide like a [ __ ]
hey [ __ ]
Mindy is my girlfriend wanna suck my
balls
maybe it was a mistake of me coming back
here after all I just wanted to see you
again but if you hate me so much I guess
I should leave
wait sir Flora is adopted is that why
her skin is blue
yes you heard that right [ __ ] my wife
and I adopted Flora many years ago
actually no we didn't adopt her we saved
her it was many years ago back when we
all still lived on Mobius before coming
here to earth I had taken my family on
an expedition to the Emerald peninsula
there have been Pixies sightings all
over the area and I knew that if I could
catch just one pixie and sail it as a
slave to some wealthy aristocrat then my
family and I would be set for life of
course those were just rumors none of us
were actually sure we were going to find
a pixie after all Pixies are nothing but
myth and then I walked over behind the
tree to take a [ __ ] and right there
under my smelly ass was a baby a pixie
baby I almost pooped in her mouth but
luckily I didn't she looked like a big
hairy ball sack with the way she was
wrapped up in the blanket I took the
baby to my wife and we debated about
what to do with it we knew we couldn't
sell it for a high price back home
because it was just a baby but we also
knew that if we left it here out in the
forest it would buy
we searched for nine full days for this
baby's parent we eventually came across
a pixie village deep in the forest we
asked the villagers where this baby's
parents were and they told us that her
mother a pink pixie was caught having
sex with a blue pixie so they had her
executed
apparently the blue Pixies and the pink
Pixies were currently at war and when
they found out one of their Pixies gave
birth to a blue pixie they had banished
the newborn pixie deep in the woods it
turns out that blue Pixies are the
equivalent of black people in human
society and the pink Pixies didn't want
the baby to live among em because they
are racist I told the Pixies that I
didn't want a baby and that they needed
to take care of it but they looked at me
cold dead in the eyes and said [ __ ] you
can take that baby back with you or you
can leave it here but if you do that
we're gonna need it we had no choice but
to take Flora back with us and raise her
as one of our own perhaps I was wrong
and coming back here to a home where I
am not welcomed I will take my leave
Flora wait are you sure you want to go
it's been so long since our whole family
has been together
I'm sure if mom was still with us she
would want all of us to be happy don't
you agree my sweet little honeyBun
he Raimondi I'll help you take your
canes upstairs Sonia said that you can
stay in her room the while you are
visiting now hold the [ __ ] up [ __ ] we
never agreed on your sister staying at
my place for the weekend mama please
I already told Mindy she could it's just
for a few days Sonia I already hate that
you hang out with the [ __ ] during the
day the last thing I want is for her to
Sleet over
she might shove one of your shoes up her
what's stopping these [ __ ] from
Sleeting at their own house
Mandy currently has a warrant out for
her arrest and the police have been
scoping out our place all week
Sonia stop crying no amount of crying is
going to make me change my mind
stop stop stop it stop that right now
that's it you're getting a timeout cup
al how many times did I have to tell you
you do not hit your mother mum
Mindy's sister said she was going to
suck my balls you are not going to ruin
this for me you are not going to ruin
this for me right over the past week
what about you Mindy what's your body
count you dirty [ __ ] do you do you want
to know well yeah that's why I asked it
then take your number multiply it by 16
and add 102 whoa you had sex with 998
guys this week your 1 was like this you
should be proud what about you [ __ ] me
well to be honest I don't really have
the time to have sex with random people
on the street like you to do I've been
too busy opening of the fakery I told
you about remember the one that mom
always dreamed of opening I'm sure
that's what mom would want of me you
know to fulfill her dream why she's dead
they not that high got a closer look at
Flora don't you guys think she looks
kind of familiar I feel like we ran into
her one time but I can't remember where
actually doesn't she look a little bit
like that pixie we met in the Emerald
peninsula you remember right the pixie
who gave us the pendant of invisibility
Sonia I think you're right are you
telling me that that pixie was Mindy's
sister all along excuse me Flora
me and my cool sips wanted to ask you
something we were talking for a little
bit and we couldn't help but notice that
you looked familiar a long time ago we
ran into a pixie in the Emerald
Peninsula she looked a lot like you
that's right I remember I did meet you
three didn't I many years ago that's
awesome we had no idea you were related
to Mindy hey do you still have the
pendant I gave you back then oh not
really
we lost that pendant a long time ago one
time my bro Manic had really bad
diarrhea he should so much that he
clogged the toilet he couldn't find the
toilet plunger so he tried using the
pendant to get it unplugged while he was
scooping up poop with the pendant he
dropped it and accidentally flushed it
well we all make mistakes from time to
time your mom just told me you three are
in a band she told you that
sweet did you listen to any of our songs
yet sorry I only listen to good music
like the Jonas Brothers and Drake now
can you believe those Hedgehogs Mindy
they're wasting their time by talking to
her when they could be talking to me hey
I've been waiting like four hours to set
your boyfriend's huge [ __ ] balls
can I go suck his [ __ ] balls right
now or what haha go right ahead one day
there's nothing stopping you he's right
over there hey green bean wanna go
upstairs and [ __ ] me in the ass like the
bad piece of broccoli you are quit
talking to that ugly [ __ ] get over here
in spank my big fat ass broccoli boy who
wants hot dogs they're fresh out of the
microwave did everybody get one mom
Sonic got like 38
shut up Sonia ha get back here you
little gremlin is that why your brother
is so fat does he always ran off with
the food yes we try not to bring food
into the same room as Sonic but I guess
mom forgot this time he always grabs
whatever is edible in a room and runs
off so no one else can have any he's
kind of like the muffin man you know
from that Nursery Rhyme run run as fast
as you can I'm gonna rape you I'm the
muffin man that's not at all
Todd the saying goes you stupid [ __ ]
these hotdogs are absolutely scrumptious
miss Hedgehog you sure do know how to
treat your guests hey when you are here
Flora were not a guest your family it's
nice to know there is somebody in the
latter family who isn't total [ __ ]
you're welcome to come around here and
play with my kids anytime you like
Wow Flora are you eating another hot dog
isn't that like your seventh one already
man I was wondering why you were so fat
I get now it makes sense
where the [ __ ] do you think you're going
get back here right now we're not done
having sex until I say we're done I'm
bored we've already had sex like six
times I want to go to Taco Bell to get a
burrito this [ __ ] crazy can you believe
her sips hey mama
drive me to Taco Bell
Mindy would it be okay if I've had a
minute of chair time cannot wait I'm
going to the strip club in five so I
want my lips to look good while I suck
balls Mindy wait you have to listen to
what I have to say it's really super
important
what the [ __ ] [ __ ] you interrupted my
makeup time nobody does that
I'm telling daddy the strip club is
going to be open soon and now I don't
have enough time to powder my big smelly
has Lindy please mom wouldn't want us
talking like that any anyway the real
reason I came here it wasn't for a union
with you guys
it's about mom what's there to talk
about man do you already told me that
she committed suicide because you are
ugly and stupid about that die I have
this VHS tape
you do remember Mandy's sixth birthday
right of course
she asked mom if she could get plastic
surgery for bigger boobs but she said no
Mundy was so mad that she shoved the
entire cake up her own ass before I
could get some that's good because I
want you to watch this I looked through
her house security cameras and I found
these
heeey it's all fuzzy just be patient
it will get there not him going you are
just wasting my time tell daddy I'll be
back late tonight [ __ ] Lindy wait look
it's starting oh my God
it's Mandy on her sixth birthday she
looks so adorable yeah and there's mom
too
now listen to what they are talking
about hey [ __ ] let me get plastic
surgery so I can have bigger boobies
Mandy you just had plastic surgery like
30 minutes ago
you can go tomorrow now let's go have
cake and open presents I want to go now
now [ __ ]
I want big-ass boobies right now if you
don't let me go now I'll [ __ ] kill
you there did you hear that Mandy said
she was going to kill her Flora she was
just mad she didn't actually mean it
it's only a coincidence
that mom was found dead in the kitchen
on Maundy sixth birthday you're in
denial I understand I was too at first
but it was one tape I have some more in
my bag like 50 of em
hey [ __ ] let me get plastic surgery
oops wrong one let me get another there
we go this is the right one you didn't
let me get bigger boobs
and now you're dead because I killed you
did you see that the blood-covered knife
and the things she said Flora there is
no proof that she said those things to
mom it could have been anyone and the
knife doesn't mean [ __ ] she could have
accidentally shoved up her own ass
thinking it was a cucumber okay I didn't
want to show you this next video but I
feel like I have to do it to get do it
to you
oh no this is yeah its mother's funeral
and look like Mandy now that I think
about it her boobs were about to
interest large but they're almost like
she had plastic surgery but mom told her
not to I don't under she has a nice tear
- Oh Flora I feel so stupid I should
have noticed something was wrong sooner
hey Mindy
I met this hot guy behind Dollar General
he said he's gonna [ __ ] my ass for 50
cents
can I borrow a camera so I can film this
[ __ ]
what the hell is going on in here Mindy
stop talking to her she's a [ __ ] hi
Mandy we were just looking through some
of our old family videos I guess you
could say we found some pretty
interesting stuff why in God's thought
are you doing that for who suggested
this Flora
she brought some tapes over
Mundy be honest with me is there
something you have been hiding from us
our entire [ __ ] lifes what is this
some kind okay interrogation it's not we
only want you to be honest with us well
I'm not talking Mandy don't do what she
don't want I'm telling daddy that you're
being [ __ ] dad hey dad get in here
what is the matter with you girls I
could hear you shouting over the sound
of my poop sloppily coming out my butt
cheeks while on the toilet in the
basement it's Flora dad she she's lying
- Mindy telling her that I killed my mom
tell her she's wrong I love mom and I
would have never done anything to hurt
her please make her stop it Flora what
the [ __ ] just I'm just appalled and
extremely disappointed in you your
sister is a kind beautiful and sexy
woman with boobs bigger than yours
why are you lying like a [ __ ] no dad
I'm not lying look here I have these VHS
tapes and they all have truths - what
happened with mom get that ball sack out
of my face do you really think I would
take your Wordle for Mandy's my own
flesh and blood daughter well guess what
you liar
you'd be wrong listen here my baby girl
what happened to mom was indeed a
tragedy but we can't continue living in
the past we have to move on and accept
that there are some things that we will
just never and I may never find the
truth of now stop being gay and
apologize to your hot sister I'll be in
the basement listening to Elvis Presley
while I lift weights and drink Cola
don't talk to me anymore today okay well
anything you want to say to me you pixie
[ __ ] sorry Mandy I guess you didn't
kill her nice apology [ __ ] you better
learn your place by the time I'm back if
you want to talk talk to this sweet ass
while I walk away
see that's right you better not accuse
my sis again you're gonna answer to me
and I warn you now that I am NOT as
forgiving as her Mindy why do you hate
me did I do something to make you mad
what do you think [ __ ] it's because
because
[Music]
because Mandy told me to
Oh No all this time Mandy told me that
you were jealous of us because we were
sexy but now I realize that Mandy is
just one big bully
I follow along with her because she told
me it's what people with huge asses do
Flora can you ever forgive me
Cayman me give me your wallet there's a
guy in the Buffalo Wild Wings parking
lot who says he won't hot wings off my
asked for only 20 bucks can you believe
that [ __ ] hey give me some more I want
to get ranch dressing dipping sauce to
Mandy look out it's a grenade someone
get this grenade out of my butt crack
Mandy are you okay it's the damn police
they finally found my ass get the [ __ ]
down or bail see you [ __ ] no God what
are we going to do they probably have
the whole place surrounded by now I'll
tell you what's gonna happen little
[ __ ] you're gonna help me make like a
fart and blow the [ __ ] out of here so
without your guns and [ __ ] because we
ain't gettin out without a fight huh
Mandy you know I don't have a gun permit
are you kidding me though well
thankfully I always carry a rifle in my
ass Mindy grab a handle of the gun and
pull it when I say go three two one go
[ __ ] Mandy should you really have an
entire rifle in your ass that almost
seems kind of like a safety hazard yeah
what if you like put something in your
ass and it goes off then I die doing
what I love
[Music]
step out of the building Mandy Latour we
don't want to use force but if you
refuse to cooperate with us we will have
no choice but to kill both you and the
rest of the civilians inside we have the
entire property surrounded so a means of
escape is impossible
do the right thing and come out with
your hands up turn yourself in and pay
for your crimes
they aren't cooperating sergeant should
we proceed with the operation that's
correct newbie killed them all we leave
no survivors let's get this done quick
so we can get back to base so you can
continue sucking on my balls
we heard glass breaking and gunshots out
front
what in the world is going on does
stupid police are here and they're
trying to take me away it's time to pick
a side
are you with me or are you against me
that's crazy what did you do
does it even matter what I [ __ ] did
grab your gun [ __ ]
Uncle Chuck look out the robot won't
children we're going to work
[Music]
does anybody else hear that it sounds
like there's a helicopter outside
Charles Mindy's dad I need both of you
to blast a hole in the ceiling would we
what would mean less talking more
shooting just do as I say if you want to
live damn it anyway it's a police
helicopter they're filming everything a
helicopter
then we need to take it down otherwise
we all have our faces on the news you're
right that's why I'm going to bring that
son of a [ __ ] down what the hell does
that blunt guy think he's doing what do
you think that sparking part lab you
[ __ ] he's going to bring this
helicopter down Dan look at Bart let me
go
he's not even trying you can do it
Barnaby save us one no Sonya take a
closer look he's not pulling the
helicopter down Bart levy is so strong
that he's pulling the entire earth up no
your fault that's not what's happening
is not putting that up but Louise Fujita
and tilaka an elderly over any galaxy
down my way even more than that
that's incredible he's doing that just
by pulling down the helicopter yes it's
pudding telly copter down son that is
creatine so provost a triplet roll the
galaxy
it's similar to what will happen if you
throw a rock into water or what happen L
taught the Titanic Terry please consult
with the press really so powerful that
it's put in everything around it now
[Music]
Holly [ __ ] dad what the [ __ ] is going on
it's like the whole galaxy is shaken I
can't tell what is vark lobby trying to
do I'll tell you what he's trying to do
he's bringing down the entire [ __ ]
galaxy he's going to ram the Sun itself
into our helicopter and kill us well
what is everybody waiting for let's end
this
don't make me do all the work like I
always do you know what just give me a
[ __ ] gun well it looks like that was
the last of em good job [ __ ] I guess
I will be heading on out of here now you
are leaving so soon but why you should
stay a little bit longer yeah
what's the rush obvious sad so the
police are after my fat ass I got a
ditch town you won't be seeing me for
some time so this is goodbye for now if
you really have to go we won't stop you
do you want to stop by home and get a
change of clothes
where I'm going I don't need clothes
daddy
I'll just hip-height by sucking a guy's
balls if I need to okay
stay safe out there my precious daughter
hey it was nice seeing you again Andy
maybe next time you're in town you can
stop by my bakery I'll give you a
discount on some muffins hey bangs and
maybe you're not as much of a total spaz
as I thought take care of yourself [ __ ]
hey Mindy
do you think she's ever coming back I'm
sure that we will see her again someday
fate works in mysterious ways
damn that a big ass like why the [ __ ]
[Music]